Hmm.
Baby,
hmm.
Look at the worm in the chocolate.
This is the second time a worm has been found in this chocolate.
This time we will have to file a case against the chocolate seller.
What time?
4:00 pm, right?
4:00 pm.
Where did you buy it from?
This is the nearby store from there.
Tell me your address.
Adarsh ​​Nagar SC Road.
Jogeshwari West.
Contact number?
Here you go sir.  Proof.
Ok.   Do
n't leave me, sir.
Absolutely.
Two hours later
Sir, is this your wife?  What happened?
Hey, you come to the police station.  I am coming.
What happened?  Why did you come back here?
Baby, look, the worm has come out and he is
not taking my complaint.
Who got the worm?
In this.
[laughter]
And how are you?   I am
fine.
Where are you coming from?   I am
coming from home.   The
car is not working.  When did you take it?  Took it just 2 days ago.   Did you learn to
drive in 2 days?   A
little bit.   It seems so.
[laughs] I would have
learned a little better.
Tomorrow is 15th August.  Everyone should come wearing good clothes.
Whoever comes wearing the best clothes will
get two laddus.
The Next Day.
Laddus also started getting distributed brother.
[laughs]
Brother, what is this
brother, packing a plate of biryani, it's a
woman's affair, Babu Bhaiya,
hey, he
even returned the money,
look, I had gone to buy biryani worth Rs. 50 and
I had given him a note of Rs. 50, but
he returned me Rs. 150, he thought
I had given him a note of Rs. 200, he was such a great
shopkeeper, friend,
you are a beggar, the poor guy is doing
business on the roadside.  You are
wasting his money.  Aren't you ashamed?  How
mean you are, friend.
Hey, leave it.  Which one is ours and if we let it be,
it is for our own benefit.
Hey, we are respectable people.  These things do
not suit us.  Come on, let's return the money.
What is brother doing?  Please come on.
Brother, you made a mistake.
Hey, let's share it among ourselves.  Walking.
You shut up.  He gave you ₹500.  You have
returned 150.  Who will pay the rest of the money?
Sorry brother, sorry.
Sorry, sack won't do?  It's my hard-earned money [laughs].
Here you go brother.
How much is this?
450.
Brother.  You didn't apply it, did you?   The
market route was closed.  Overacting
means you have to go.
[laughter]
Brother, please donate for the Sawan Bhandara.
Wait, be patient.
Sorry brother.
But one second.
Mother Shera.
[laughter]
Hey, a sandal seller came to the neighborhood.
Look and tell me how much it will cost?
Good.
Or it will be ₹50 to ₹100.
You tell me how much it costs after seeing it?   It will be worth
₹700-₹800.   It
looks like ₹700-₹800, right?  Brought it for ₹100.
[laughter] Get out of here.
I am going to work myself.  Here.
What are you looking at?  One more floor will be built above this.
Hey Bhabhi ji, your husband is cheating on you.
Talks to some other girl on call.
Hey, have you gone mad?  My husband
loves me very much.  He can never betray me.
If you don't believe it, just call and
see.  Biji will tell his number.
Ok.  I will call and see right now.  Now
milk will be milk and water will be water.
Hey, move your hands quickly, I will not give you the money.
Hi.
Hi.  What are you doing?
Hey, I have come to work.
Where is Riya busy, tell me her number?   I will
show you right now with my phone.
And wait for now.  Look at this.   The
number you have dialed
is currently busy.
Which other girl are you talking to?
Tell me now.
Hey crazy, I am talking to you only.
If you are not talking to any other girl
then why is your number showing busy?
Hey, have you gone mad?  Your call is going on
so it will show busy.   Don't
make me mad.  I am very educated.
tell truth.
What?  What should I do with it?
You should come home.  I will break your bones.
[laughter]
Hey, where did you get this idiot from?  The
thinking of wearing modern clothes is still like that of a village girl.
Babuji, we both got married.
Son, weren't you ashamed of marrying her?
Babuji, why should I feel ashamed?
Hey bastard, I am talking to this girl.
My country, my nation, this is my homeland.
Brother, give me a tricolor flag.
Yellow.  How much is it?
50 is too much, man.  Today is 15th August.
Do something less.
Come on, I will give this to you for free.
But tell me one thing, who wrote Jana Gana Mana
?
Take this for ₹50.  [laughter]
Yes, brother.  How much is it?
You have got ₹10, brother.
Yes.  Yellow.
Hey friend, I don't have ₹10 change.
You do one thing.  Eat another ₹10.  Okay,
bring it and feed it to me.  Here you go [music] brother.
[Music]
Okay brother,
yes,
but wait a second,
oh brother, you cheat [Laughter]
you bastard [Laughter]
[Music]
Dude, she's a very beautiful girl.  We will have to talk to him.
Go and
excuse me.   Yes.   If
you don't mind, can
I help you lift it?   Please do it.
Ok.
[sound of clearing throat]
What happened?  I am not getting up.
Yes, he is getting up, he is getting up.
Yes.
By the way, where do you live?   Right
here behind.   It's a
good
time.  Let me ask.  By the way, do you have a
boyfriend?   It was there,
now it is not there.
Wow, what a smile.   I will be the one to
woo her.
By the way, what is there in this box that weighs so much
?
My boyfriend is in this.
[laughter]
Brother, give me three crisps and four chips.
Okay, wait.
Four chips?  Three crisps.
Give me four packets of gems.
Give me four gems and four center prices also.
Four center prices.
How much money is it brother?
60 + 8 makes your ₹68.
How much is 68 ₹68?
Eight.
I don't know either.  Wait, let me do something.
Brother, I will give you only ₹500.
Oh okay, give it to me.  Come and give me ₹500.
Yes, I will not give even ₹1 more than this.
But madam, I will not give you so much
money in future.  I am giving it to you this time only.
Chala [laughs]
Thank you brother.
Oh, thank you madam.  If such customers
come every day, I will become rich in two days.
[Music]
Hey brother, please give me the five rupee Maggi.
Hey Bhabhi ji, you here?
Hey brother, what's the matter, he has been transferred here,
right?  So I have to stay here for now.
Oh wow, that's great.  What do you have to give?   The one with
five is the same.  Yellow.   Take
this money brother.
Oh, leave it.  So this money is my own
shop.   Okay, then
give me the bigger one.
Yellow.
Ok.  So I will also give you an oil bottle.
[laughter]
Then the same thing comes up, the poor man.
You're poor because of your habits [laughs].
[laughter] Are
you crazy, you've parked your car in the driveway
?
But madam, we are inside the car.
Quiet, absolutely quiet.  Because of you boys, we
girls get a bad name that we do
n't know how to drive.
This is also my mistake.
O brother, kill me, kill me, kill me.
Women:
Wow brother, you brought the car today.  how how?  Hey, it's
not like that brother.  Papa had gone away with my bike, so today I had to bring the
car.
Well, this doesn't cause sunburn, right?  Yes, it is cool.   It started to
become a habit [music].
Hey, when did you post the story?
Brother, just drive it like this in summer.   Same
thing again.  Brother, you become poor.  Bring it
brother, give it to me.
Friend, I don't have any money.
Stop the car, stop.  Stop the car.  Don't have money?
No, brother.   Come down.  Get down.
Hey bastard, do you ever have money in your pocket or
not?  Will you roam around for free?  Get
out of here.  Get out.  Come on brother, you
drive the car.   I do
n't know how to drive, friend.   Hey,
you go.
Brother, I also don't know how to drive.
Hey brother, you should have told me, if you do
n't have money then tell me in advance, I will make arrangements,
I also have not brought the money and if you
do this then how will things work out
[laughs] it is
good that Dheeraj went to school today, otherwise he would have
insulted me even today, he would have insulted me even today, he would have insulted me a
lot in the restaurant, I
know that you will come to the restaurant, that is why I have run away
from school again and again, come
[sound of clearing throat]
what will you eat sir?
Sir, what will you feed me today?  She will come home.  Asking
what will you feed me?  [laughter] Sir, please bring four plates of
Paneer Maggi.
OK sir.  Here you go sir, your Paneer Maggi.
Sir, please take this water.
Sir, let me have some water.  I keep water in my school bag.
[laughter]
Here you go, Sir Bill.  Here you go, sir.  Sir,
take this sir.
Good.
Whose card should he take?  There are so many cards.
Which card is this?  G
National Insurance Scheme.
Your card
brother,
this is fine.   I have
gas in my stomach.
[laughter] You
come to eat in the restaurant, this person
lying in the shop right now, do you know who he is,
who is a
millionaire, a millionaire, a
millionaire [laughter] A
millionaire is trapped in your net,
hey, only millionaires get trapped, do
n't you believe it
[laughter]
Today is 15th August,
whoever wants to eat jalebi, come to school,
jalebi
[music]
Hey, you will enjoy it,
but give me one second
sir, give me jalebi too,
jalebi, jalebi is over,
no joke, no seriously, no
joke, make our life hell,
for whom did you leave all this
[laughter]
Come on Bhabhi, I am leaving, then
what, didi, didi, I have come for only two days.   Wait at
least for a month.
Hey, what should I do Bhabhi, I also feel like
staying for a month but I can't wait.
Sister, are you sure you want to stay for a month
?
Yes, yes, I really feel like
staying there for a month.  Sister, you have to stay for a
month.
Yes, yes, why not.
Sister, I am asking for the last time.  You definitely have to wait for
a month.
Oh yes, yes, absolutely.  Well then.
Look sister, brother has made
arrangements for us to stay for a month.
Yes.  We will gossip a lot, right?
[laughs]
Oh brother,
yes tell me, will you get
Balushahi?
Yes, you will get it. Tell me how much should I give you,
but brother, I don't have money.
Okay brother, no problem, take this.
Hey brother, I was just checking whether
humanity is still alive in the world [music] or not.
I have money, take this.
Okay,
hey brother, give that sand here.
Hey brother, but why?
Hey brother, at least give it to me.
Hey, such a different fraud is going on.  Here you go
brother.
Hey brother, please give me that Balushahi.
Why did you give this one?
Hey brother, that Balushahi is 10 days old.
Break the bastard's skull.  Break his skull.
Put it in your penis like this.  Hey brother, are
you done?
We will take it.   Please
parcel it.
Yes brother, yes yes, oh my
god, such a beautiful saree.  Who is it for
?
For whom?  They were brought to you.   I am
not doing any drama like Raj.   Don't
think like brother.  Okay, right?  You didn't
bring a saree for even one person.  I will bring four more sarees now.   Oh my God,
you don't earn.
Where are you getting so much money from?  Brother,
hey mom, I have sold your silver bulls.
[laughter]
Here's your stuff, sister.  How much money is it,
sister?  ₹69.
69?  What is this?  What did
sister ask?
Hello Google.  What is 69 called in English
?
Wow, sister.  It will go well, take this
sister, how much is your 69 69?
What did he ask me?
Hello Google, what is 69 called in Hindi
?
Okay sister.
[laughs]
What a stupid daughter-in-law he has brought.
Yes, I am a fool, Mom.
Even left my home.  Changed the name also.  He
bore the expenses of the marriage and also gave dowry.   I am
also hearing abuses in my in-laws' house.   I am
also serving my in-laws.  I am doing all the household
work and if I have to go somewhere, I am asking.
I am very stupid and do you
know who made it?  Your son.   I have started
irritating everyone so much.
Brother, can I get samosa?
Yes brother, you will get it.
But brother, there is a problem.
What's the problem?  I don't have money.
Okay, no
problem, you can eat this.
But brother, I have money.  I was just trying to
see if there is humanity in this world or
not.  Here, take your money.
Okay, do one thing, return the samosas.
Why?
Hey, give it to me.
Take this.
Yellow.
Hey brother, give me that one.  Why did you
give this one?
It was a week old.  [laughter]
A week old.
Hey son, where did you go all night?
Hey, Papa was at Chhotu's house, he was there at night.
The Next Day.
Hey son, it's so late and you have
n't come home yet.
Hey dad, we were doing some group study at Chhotu's house.
We will come in the morning.   The
bastard says every day that he is at Chhotu's place.   It is at
Chhotu's place.  He is not hiding anything from
us, is he?
The Next Day.
Babu, you are saying the right thing.  No.  Hey
son, where were you last night?
You will make a group call to Chhotu at his house.
[laughter]
Brother,
yes, little brother.
Hey Rocky Bhai, we were about to call you.  Please
tell my father that I was
studying with you at your house at night.
Oh brother, betrayal.   Take
this water brother-in-law.
Hey sister-in-law, we have come to our in-laws' house for the first time and
you will give us water in a glass?  Good?
Yes.
Wait, let me bring it.   Bring it.   Wait a minute.
Our sister-in-law is very nice.
say anything.
Hey, it will be fun.
Wait a minute.  Be patient.   It
's okay now brother-in-law.
This is it, sister-in-law.  Bring it.
Hey Lalli, where is this toilet bag?
[laughter]
Madam, give me one.  Bread.
Brother,
yes
I bought a bridge for ₹80 and it returned me ₹90.
Hey, aren't you ashamed?  You took some poor man's
money like this.  Hey poor girl, she
works hard all day and then earns some money
and you are being dishonest with her.
You should have returned it at that time itself.
Why did you bring it?  Hey, you should have
thought a little.  I got into the habit of eating haram food.  Hey, this
is haram.  Haram.  We do not eat haram things.
Let's go and return the money.
Yes brother, you are right.  Let's go and bring it.   Come on,
madam.
Yes.
Do you keep using your mobile all day long?  Are
you not paying attention to your work?   Yes
?  This child gave you a ₹500 note.
500?
And you are giving him back ₹90.   Aren't you
ashamed?  [laughter] Hey, why are you
sitting with the shop open?  Buy a gun and
shoot the customer and snatch the money.  [laughter]
Sir, why are you being so hyper?  I will give you Rs 200 for Rs 90.
Here, take your money.   Be
careful next time.  Don't do this
with children.   Okay
okay.  Sorry sir.  Sir, don't shout.
No problem.
Where are you?  Hey, someone died in the village.
Now I will eat the whole vegetable with great force.
I will eat Puri and Bundi after pressing it.  Have
n't met him for a long time.
Brother, your father is no more.
[screaming sound]
[laughter]
Give me ₹15, son, you haven't eaten anything for two days,
Baba is not with me, go ahead,
give it to me, son, God has given you a good
husband, your
husband ran away with his Laila and
left me,
give it to me, son, by the grace of God, your
business is running well, the
whole family is in debt, Baba, oh my god,
give it to me, son, your father is happy,
father is in jail, Baba,
give it to me, son, your younger sister is there
herself.   It is my
younger sister who has run away with my husband,
Baba.
Hey grandfather,
I don't understand one thing.  If
using mobile phones is not allowed at petrol pumps, then
why is the facility of online payment provided?
Why did you love her when you knew she would betray you?
Today's pack is in the name of the country's independence.
Ali,
your Pakistan is long live, we have
no objection to this, but our Hindustan
was long live, is long live and will remain long live.
Hindustan is long live,
shut up, sell the free bungalow.   It will be
sold.  By the way, what is the rate?
₹ Crore.
₹ Crore.  ₹ crore is too much.  Do one work and get it done
for one crore.
No, one crore is very less.  Do one thing, neither
yours nor mine, get it done for ₹1.5 crore.   That's
ok.
Hello Czech.
Sign on equals right?
Yes sign on is equal to.  He is fine.
But in whose name should this bungalow be registered?   Oh,
he'll keep coming.  Look, he has come.
Which bungalow is it?
This is the bungalow.
How much is it?
50 million.
50 million.  5 crore is too much.  Get it done for Rs 3 crore.
3 crores will be too less
brother.  So neither yours nor mine is final for Rs 3.5 crore.   That's
ok.
Rahil Bhai, please transfer the bungalow in his name.
Hey, I have applied lime.   Neither a
doctor nor an engineer nor in slavery of the government.  There is
money only
in brokerage.   Wait a minute.
[screaming]
Free clothes for blind girls.
Let me go inside and get the clothes.
Hey brother, is there anyone in the shop?
Yes, tell me madam, what should I show you?
Hey brother, please show me the clothes.
Hey madam, are you blind?
Yes, I am blind.
Hey madam, this is the rule of our shop.  We do
not give free clothes to blind girls.
Tell me what should I show you?
Hey, show me anything.  Which one do I
see anyway?
Ok.  I'll tell you one minute.
Look at this madam, this will look very good on you.
Yes, okay.  I can't see it.  You
pack it.
Hey madam, please go to the trial room once and
try it.  Sometimes the size becomes smaller or bigger.
Yes friend, let me check the size.  Otherwise what is the point of
free clothes?
Ok.  Okay, drop me to the trial room.
Ok, good.  Come.
Yes.
And wait for now.
Come madam, come.   Here are the
clothes madam.
Madam, I closed the changing room gate.
You can change comfortably.   The
bastard made me stand outside the changing room.
Now how do I change my clothes in front of him
?
[laughs]
Hey Khebari, there are 50 people like you
in a day.  Understood?  Bring the cloth here.  Come on, go away.
[laughter]
Oh, brother.
Yes.
What are you eating?
Chocolate.
Hey, give it to me too.
Will you eat chocolate?
Yes.
First tell Papa, then I will give it to you.   You
bastard,
tell me papa,
I am
also making a video,
papa, is
this some aunty,
papa,
papa, are
you married,
hi, this is my papa [laughs] hey, he is
lying, this bastard who
asks mummy's name, how can he be my son,
hey mummy, papa,
hey father [laughs]
show me dreams, ask sir.  Hey, listen.
Yes.   There is no
milk left at home, go and get some milk from the market.   Ca
n't you see I am doing household work.
But milk will have to be brought.
How many times have I told you to learn to ride a scooter?
You can do the housework yourself.
When my work is being done by using my tongue, then
why should I ride a scooter?
[laughs]
Give me a four jalebi too.
One second.
And brother, please let me eat jalebi too.  One of them has a
child in her womb and is carrying him.
Okay, brother.  Tell me which month it is.
[laughs]
Hey Vishram
Sir, he came from another school to eat laddus at his school.
[laughter]
Sir, should I pick it up when you're done?   I revived it.   Get it
packed.
Ok sir.
Son, recite poetry.
Sir is not coming.
If you don't know poetry then you will have to sing.
You will have to play the game.  [laughs]
He fooled me by making me recharge.
He made a fool of me by making me recharge it.
I am Baba Tillu.
[laughs]
I've eaten enough gutkha, now I'll eat paan.
I have eaten enough gutkha, now I will eat paan.   Do
n't do this my love.
How is the world?  What are these gaps?  Please remove it.
How is the world?  What are these
gaps?  Please remove it.
What color underwear are you wearing?  Please tell me.
Brother, now look
sir, I have a question,
sir, the one who was born on 15th August, was he born
or was he liberated [laughs]
guys today's video ends here,
tell me in the comments which clip you found the
funniest, otherwise I had made this video even
longer than before so that I
could make you guys laugh even more,
so brother, so much hard work has gone into making this video today,
brother, you guys
cannot even imagine.  Let me show you one
thing first.  You will notice.  Only
after that will you support me.  I will show you.  Let me
remove the 'ph' first.  Look brother, look at this
FK light, I am shooting here with it out.
And I am sitting right here.  Look brother, there are
two stands installed here.  The mirror
[sound of clearing throat] is on.  And I
sit here and shoot videos.  Just look.
You people might be thinking that I have a lot of stuff.  There
is a lot of money etc.  So
brother, there is nothing like that.  It takes a lot of hard work.
Look how hot it is now.  So friend, if you liked the
video then please like it.
Subscribe and support the channel.   The
rest is the same setup.  If you need to buy stuff,
I have tagged you.  Buy it.